<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Astronomical Software Development</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Astronomical Software Development</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 10:23:06 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Program</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 10:23:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/program/</guid><description>Program The preliminary schedule for this program is available here.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 10:23:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/about/</guid><description>About What this workshop is =&amp;gt; This will be a week-long workshop and unconference, where we will discuss and learn about the finer details of managing and contributing to open source software projects in astronomy. This program aims to:
build a network of astronomers who participate in the open source community, through contributions including code, documentation, support, management, and many other aspects of this ecosystem, identify ways that we, as a community, can promote and support astronomical software development, and the people who do it, and discuss some high-level technical topics specific to scientific software development (e.</description></item><item><title>Logistics</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/logistics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 10:25:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/logistics/</guid><description>Logistics This workshop will be held in person at the Center for Computational Astrophysics in New York City, May 16–20, 2022.
Please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to contact Dan Foreman-Mackey, the chair of the organizing committee, with any comments, questions, or suggestions!</description></item><item><title>Organizing committee</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/organizers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 10:25:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/organizers/</guid><description>Organizing committee Kelle Cruz Dan Foreman-Mackey (chair) Christina Hedges Rodrigo Luger Adrian Price-Whelan</description></item><item><title>Other workshops, courses, and resources</title><link>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/resources/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:25:03 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://code.astrodata.nyc/pages/resources/</guid><description>Other workshops, courses, and resources As discussed above, this workshop is not designed to cover all topics in scientific software development. Below we include a list of other workshops and resources that may also be of interest. You are encouraged to open a pull request at astrodatagroup/code if you have other resources to recommend.
Workshops:
The Carpentries Python in Astronomy Code/Astro AstroHackWeek SciPy annual conference (see the tutorials) Books and online resources:</description></item></channel></rss>